<content>
	<description>Why You Need a Micro Frontend Platform for Kubernetes</description>
	<typeCode>NWS</typeCode>
	<typeDescription>News</typeDescription>	
	<mainGroup>free</mainGroup>
	<attributes>
		<attribute xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:type="jaxbDateAttribute">
			<name>date</name>
			<type>Date</type>
			<value>2020-09-01T00:00:00+02:00</value>
		</attribute>
		<attribute xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:type="jaxbTextAttribute">
			<name>title</name>
			<type>Text</type>
			<value>Why You Need a Micro Frontend Platform for Kubernetes</value>
			<roles>
				<role>jacms:title</role>
			</roles>
		</attribute>
		<attribute xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:type="jaxbHypertextAttribute">
			<name>abstract</name>
			<type>Hypertext</type>
			<htmlValue>
			<![CDATA[
			<p> In a world where customers will abandon your brand after even one bad online experience, constantly innovating UX is essential to any business plan. However, when your organization builds large web apps with a monolithic structure, it can be difficult to respond to user needs in real time.</p>
			]]>
			</htmlValue>
		</attribute>
		<attribute xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:type="jaxbHypertextAttribute">
			<name>body</name>
			<type>Hypertext</type>
			<htmlValue>
			<![CDATA[
			<p> In a world where customers will abandon your brand after even one bad online experience, constantly innovating UX is essential to any business plan. However, when your organization builds large web apps with a monolithic structure, it can be difficult to respond to user needs in real time. To overcome this challenge, many IT leaders have opted for a more modular approach to development. Building applications with micro frontends in a Kubernetes environment can help you structure your organization into independent teams that have control over a particular business function within a larger app at every layer of the stack. In so doing, you allow your decision making units to be smaller, which enables your organization to innovate more quickly overall. So then why do you need a micro frontend platform for Kuberntes? What does a platform add that enhances this process?  Here are 3 compelling reasons your enterprise needs a micro frontend platform.</p>
			]]>
			</htmlValue>
		</attribute>
		<attribute xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:type="jaxbResourceAttribute">
			<type>Image</type>
			<name>image</name>
			<resource>
				<text>Entando at Work</text>
				<path>/test-image-rest/resources/cms/images/sample-image-1_d0.jpg</path>
				<resourceId>entandoAtWork</resourceId>
				<restResourcePath>http://localhost:8080/test-image-rest/api/rs/en/jacms/image?id=entandoAtWork</restResourcePath>
			</resource>	
		</attribute>
		<attribute xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:type="jaxbTextAttribute">
			<name>category</name>
			<type>Text</type>
			<value>PRODUCT</value>
		</attribute>
	</attributes>
	<lastEditor>admin</lastEditor>
</content>
